[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What popular singer and actress received the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actress for her role in the 1986 film Shanghai Surprise?", "correct_answer": "Madonna", "incorrect_answers": ["Barbra Streisand", "Cher", "Gloria Estefan"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Trading Places, there was a prostitute named Ophelia. What actress played the part of Ophelia?", "correct_answer": "Jamie Lee Curtis", "incorrect_answers": ["Jamie Lynn Spears", "Betty Thomas", "Gina Gershon"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ripe fruits of raspberry culitvars come in all of these colors except which one?", "correct_answer": "Green", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellow", "Black", "Purple"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Despite a hurricane\u2019s destructive nature and its toll on both lives and property, there are some beneficial effects of tropical cyclones.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Atticus Finch was a great, moral man and a fine lawyer who defended Tom Robinson. In which novel and  movie was he a central character?", "correct_answer": "To Kill a Mockingbird", "incorrect_answers": ["The Trial", "Witness for the Prosecution", "Anatomy of a Murder"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of food does the Lesser Vasa Parrot, also known as Black Parrot, feed on?", "correct_answer": "Fruit", "incorrect_answers": ["Insects", "All of these", "Carrion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For which of the following two movies did Denzel Washington win Oscars?", "correct_answer": "Glory and Training Day", "incorrect_answers": ["Cry Freedom and The Hurricane", "The Mighty Quinn and A Soldiers Story", "Malcolm X and Philadelphia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The origin of the Chinese Crested dog is unknown, but according to some sources it may have come from which of these places?", "correct_answer": "Mexico and Africa", "incorrect_answers": ["Canada and USA", "Thailand and Egypt", "Japan and China"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which movie does Edward James Olmos play a teacher in Los Angeles who gets an entire class of low-income, Hispanic students to pass the Advanced Placement Calculus test?", "correct_answer": "Stand and Deliver", "incorrect_answers": ["Proof", "Stand By Me", "Pi"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The performance of this actor in a 1988 movie brought him the Golden Raspberry Award for Worst Actor.", "correct_answer": "Sylvester Stallone in Rambo III", "incorrect_answers": ["Burt Reynolds in Rent-A-Cop", "Jackie Mason in Caddyshack II", "Tom Cruise in Cocktail"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor portrayed Paris in the 2004 movie Troy, based on Homers Iliad?", "correct_answer": "Orlando Bloom", "incorrect_answers": ["Brad Pitt", "Sean Bean", "Peter OToole"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is Indiana Jones real name as revealed in the movie The Last Crusade?", "correct_answer": "Henry Jones Jr.", "incorrect_answers": ["John Jacob Jones", "Indiana Jones Jr.", "Jack Jones"]}]